/*
Collection 1: candidates 
Procedure   : just create the collection 
*/

/*
Collection 2: questionnaire 
Procedure   : push individual questions into your mlab database
*/



/* Question 1 */
{
    "question": "Maximum size of a single S3 object",
    "option1": "No Limit",
    "option2": "5 TB",
    "option3": "5 GB",
    "option4": "100 GB",
    "ans": "option1"
}

/* Question 2 */
{
    "question": "What is part of a database that holds only one type of information",
    "option1": "Report",
    "option2": "Field",
    "option3": "Record",
    "option4": "File",
    "ans": "option2"
}

/* Question 3 */
{
    "question": "What does VVVF stand for",
    "option1": "Variant Voltage Vile Frequency",
    "option2": "Variable Velocity Variable Fun",
    "option3": "Very Very Vicious Frequency",
    "option4": "Variable Voltage Variable Frequency",
    "ans": "option4"
}

/* Question 4 */
{
    "question": "What frequency range is the High Frequency band",
    "option1": "100 kHz",
    "option2": "1 GHz",
    "option3": "30 to 300 MHz",
    "option4": "3 to 30 MHz",
    "ans": "option4"
}

/* Question 5 */
{
    "question": "Who developed Yahoo",
    "option1": "Dennis Ritchie & Ken Thompson",
    "option2": "David Filo & Jerry Yang",
    "option3": "Vint Cerf & Robert Kahn",
    "option4": "Steve Case & Jeff Bezos",
    "ans": "option2"
}

/* Question 6 */
{
    "question": "What does the term PLC stand for",
    "option1": "Programmable Lift Computer",
    "option2": "Program List Control",
    "option3": "Programmable Logic Controller",
    "option4": "Piezo Lamp Connector",
    "ans": "option3"
}

/* Question 7 */
{
    "question": " DB computer abbreviation usually means",
    "option1": "Database",
    "option2": "Double Byte",
    "option3": "Data Block",
    "option4": "Driver Boot",
    "ans": "option1"
}

/* Question 8 */
{
    "question": ".INI extension refers usually to what kind of file",
    "option1": "Image file",
    "option2": "System file",
    "option3": "Hypertext related file",
    "option4": "Image Color Matching Profile file",
    "ans": "option2"
}

/* Question 9 */
{
    "question": "Who created Pretty Good Privacy (PGP)",
    "option1": "Phil Zimmermann",
    "option2": "Tim Berners-Lee",
    "option3": "Marc Andreessen",
    "option4": "Ken Thompson",
    "ans": "option1"
}

/* Question 10 */
{
    "question": " .TMP extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
    "option1": "Compressed Archive file",
    "option2": "Image file",
    "option3": "Temporary file",
    "option4": "Audio file",
    "ans": "option3"
}
